https://alaskajewelry.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We take every precaution to protect your information. We utilize the highest security standards in the industry with military grade 2048 bit RSA public/private key pair data encryption and server certificate authentication. All orders are processed with Secure Sockets Layer Technology.
And your other personal information?
It’s safe too. Your personal information is your personal information. We don’t collect more than we need, and we don’t share what we collect. We are the sole owner of the information collected on this site, and we won’t share it with others unless we are required to do so by law (i.e. Federal or state criminal investigation).
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, promotions, etc. However, you may opt-out at any time by clicking the unsubscribe button at the bottom of your emails.
We request information from you when you place an order via this web site or on the telephone (like name, telephone number and shipping/billing address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we use this contact information to get in touch with you.
Still don’t feel secure with purchasing online?
No problem. Just call us toll free 1-800-360-5744 and we can take your order over the phone.
This privacy policy is subject to change. While you will not be personally notified if our privacy policy changes, the most current version of our policy can always be found on this web page.
Stay Connected!
Success!
Select the fields to be shown. Others will be hidden. Drag and drop to rearrange the order.
ImageSKURatingPriceStockAvailabilityAdd to cartDescriptionContentWeightDimensionsAttributes
Compare
